It seems today that all you see
Is violence in movies and sex on TV
But where are those good old-fashioned values
On which we used to rely?
Lucky there's a family guy
Lucky there's a man who positively can do...
呃 呃 等等 等等
Uh, uh, hold it.Hold it.
怎…怎么回事
What-what...what's going on here?
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
潜规则了吧 傻逼了吧
你…你什么
You...you're what?
是啊
Yeah.
我们正演到一半呢
We're in the middle of a thing here.
但你一直没回我的短信
Well, you didn't return any of my texts.
那这…这是怎么回事
So what-what...so what's going on?
你…你想…想要我载你一程
You-you...you want,like,a...a ride to the place?
Peter 怎么回事
Peter,what's going on?
怎么回事 Lois 就是这女孩
What's going on, Lois,is that this girl
明显不太舒服 而且我接到通知
is obviously not well,and I have just learned
说她一直在偷这个节目组的东西
that she's been stealing from the show,
她应该马上被带出去
and she should probably be escorted out of the building.
Family Guy 10x01
Lottery Fever
Nah, nah
Family Guy.
中文字幕:wudixny 校对:wudixny zurica 注释:wudixny zurica
后期:wudixny 压制:wudixny  @familyguy贴吧字幕组
现在我们回到
ANNOUNCER (over TV):We now return
为山羊剪辑的星际迷航2:可汗之怒版本
to Star Trek II:The Wrath of Khan,edited for goats.
永远被放逐于
KHAN(over speaker):Marooned for all eternity
死星的中心
in the center of a dead planet.
被活埋掉
Buried alive.
Lois 我需要2万8千刀
Lois, I need $28,000.
用来干什么
For what?
我决定开一家寿司店
I've decided I want to open a sushi restaurant.
你对于寿司知道些什么
What do you know about sushi?
我才不关心什么寿司呢
I don't care about the sushi.
我是只想当顾客走进门时对他们吼叫
I just want to yell at customers when they walk in the door.
("初次见面"神马的)
来了个黑哥们
Here comes a black guy!
Peter你别想拿到钱
Peter, you're not getting money
不管是开店还是其他任何事
for that or anything else.
我们现在已经基本没什么现钱了
We're running seriously low on cash right now.
事实上 我可能不得不去找个全职工作了
In fact,I may have to get my own full-time job.
天啊 我们已经拮据到这种程度了
Geez.Are we really living that close to the edge?
你知道的啊 Brian
You know we are, Brian.
不然你以为我们为什么等那么长时间
Why do you think we waited so long
才在上个月才带你去宠物美容店
to take you to the groomer's last month?
嘿 是不是该给我去剔个毛了
Hey,isn't it time for me to get a haircut?
哦 不用吧 我想你不是才去过么
Oh,no.I think you just got one.
你确定
Are you sure?
因为我觉得我的指甲真的很长了
'Cause I feel like my nails are really long.
好吧 我会留意的 但我肯定
Yeah,I'll check,but I'm pretty sure
再过个1 2周也不要紧
it's not for another couple of weeks.
现在是什么日子了
What day is this?
不管你愿不愿意 我们这段时间
Like it or not,we're going to have to start
得用有限的开支度日了
living on a strict budget for a while.
晚上好 我是Tom Tucker 这里是
Good evening.I'm Tom Tucker,and this is...
新闻…
News...
我以为你会和我一起唱的 Joyce
I thought you were going to sing with me, Joyce.
好吧 今日头条新闻
Okay. Our top story tonight.
罗德岛州彩票
The Rhode Island State Lottery
声称头奖已经累积到150,000,000刀的奖金了
has climbed to a record $150 million jackpot.
没错 Tom
That's right, Tom.
强力球的热潮已经正式席卷Quahog了
Powerball fever has officially gripped Quahog.
美一种彩票
我们派遣了第五频道新闻亚洲记者
We sent Channel Five News Asian correspondent
Tricia Takanawa在镇上采访民众的反应
Tricia Takanawa around town to get the public reaction.
Wset市长 如果你赢了彩票准备干什么
Mayor West,what do you plan to do if you win the lottery?
呃 我肯定会很炫耀地给自己置办一身
Well, I'd finally splurge and buy myself
那种高档的4件式套装
one of those fancy four-piece suits.
我想加入你们的乡村俱乐部
I'd like to join your country club.
我想这肯定不会有问题的
I assume that won't be a problem.
那你们呢 世上仅存的每个波斯(现称伊朗)人
And how about you,every Persian guy in the world?
当然是白色的BMW(宝马)啦
ALL:White BMW.
就是这样 Lois
There you go, Lois.
那就是解决我们困境的办法
That's the answer right there.
只要我们赢得彩票就行了
We'll just win the lottery.
事实上 我现在就要去买我那中奖彩票了
In fact,I'm going to go buy my winning ticket right now.
Peter 怎么了
Peter, what's wrong?
没…呃…没什么
It's, uh, nothing.
我要等一会
I'm just going to wait a minute.
外面有一些穿紧身牛仔裤的小青年
There's teenagers in skinny jeans out there.
大伙们 我有好消息要说
Everyone, I got big news.
我们要发财了
We are going to be rich.
天啊 peter
Oh, my God, Peter.
你买了成千张彩票
There are thousands of lottery tickets here.
你哪来的钱买这些的
Where did you get the money for all these?
简单 我把我们的房子第二次抵押了
Simple.I took out a second mortgage on the house.
什么 Peter 你傻了啊
What?!Peter, this is idiotic.
你赢的几率只有百万分之一
Your odds of winning are like 100 million to one.
你难道不知道彩票是傻子交的另一个税么
Don't you know the lottery is just a tax on stupid people?
如果奖品是
Would you be saying that if the prize
1亿5千万包邻居家的垃圾你还会这么说吗(狗的爱好)
was 150 million bags of the neighbor's garbage?
但不是啊
But it's not.
我…我是说 有么
I mean... I mean, is it?
这…这完全是个不切实际而且不搭界的问题
It's... that-that is an unrealistic,unfair question.
Peter Brian是对的
Peter, Brian's right.
你怎么能这样不负责任
How can you be so irresponsible?
你马上把这些彩票退回去
You take these tickets back right now.
没门 lois
No way, Lois.
我们会赢的
We're going to win.
我在劳军表演时结了
I got lots of good karma built up
很多的善缘
from doing those USO shows.
USO=United Services Organization是美国劳军联合组织
所以 显然 他们找到了
So, apparently, they found
一种大规模破坏性武器 我的轻击杆
a weapon of mass destruction-- my putter.
好了 小伙子们 去搞定他们吧
All right,boys.Go get 'em over there.
现在 有请 Burce Jenner先生
And now, please welcome Mr. Bruce Jenner.
美前奥运会田径运动员 获得过10项全能金牌
现在是演说家 公众 电视名人
模仿了欧美卡通里大灰狼发情的片段
只是想提醒你们一下
Just wanted to remind you fellas
在为什么而战斗
what you're all fighting for.
好了 就是现在 大伙们
Okay,this is it,you guys.
他们要宣布获奖的彩票号码了
They're going to announce the winning lottery numbers.
Griffin一家命中注定的时刻到了
Time for the Griffin family to meet its destiny.
我们输了的话 我要和你离婚
When we lose,I'm getting a divorce.
了解
Understood.
我们现在在演播室里直播 一个穿着
We're here live in our studio where a checkout girl
廉价衣服想要成为模特的收银女孩
in a cheap dress who wants to be a model
准备好抽出中奖号码了
is ready to draw the winning numbers.
"E!"
那是个3 亲爱的
TUCKER:That's a three,honey.
转过来
Turn it around.
这个
This.
Thirty-one.
恐怖鬼魂的嘴巴
Spooky ghost mouth.
那是个0
That's a zero.
雪人
Snowman.
Eight.
2艘帆船
Two sailboats.
Forty-four.
Seventeen.
不 那是… 哦 对 就是17
No,that's...Oh, yes, that is 17.
她挺善于认17的
She's good at 17.
好了 各位 这些就是中奖号码
Well,folks,those are our winning numbers.
祝那些所有…
Good luck to all of our...
Twenty-four!
不 就那样了 已经结束了
No,that's it. We're done.
观众请不要算上24
Anyone watching,do not count 24.
煎饼
pancakes
好吧 我不知道他在干嘛
OK,I don't know what she's doing now.
来人把那机器关了
Somebody turn the machine off.
N…Nikki Nikki 好了 可以了
N-Nikki,Nikki,that's good.That's good.
去…去我的车里等着(到处都是潜规则呀)
Go... go wait in my car.
行了 你干得不错
All right, you did good.
准备带她去Walt烤牛肉店的
Going to take her to Walt's Roast Beef.
好了 孩子们 现在我们有20万张
All right,kids,we got 200,000
彩票要检查
lottery tickets we got to check.
好了 你们准备怎么弄
All right,how do you want to do this?
一个房子的静态镜头 然后时间从晚上到了白天
A static shot of the house where night turns into day
还是来点蒙太奇的歌曲来详细解释下我们在干嘛
or a montage song that over-explains what we're doing?
呃 第二个
Um,that second one
听起来还不错
sounds like it could be funny.
检查彩票
Checking lottery tickets
核对数字
Looking at the numbers
看是不是对的上新闻里的那些
And seeing if they match the ones on the news
如果是的 那我们就是赢家
If they do,then we're winners
如果不是 我们就把它们
If they don't,then we put them
放在特定的一摞
In the designated pile
给我们那些已经检查过的彩票
For tickets we already checked
这持续了很久
This is taking forever
所以Brian在打哈欠
That's why Brian is yawning
Stewie在揉眼睛
And Stewie's rubbing his eyes
蒙太奇快结束了
The montage is almost over
所以音乐和歌声
That's why the music and the vocals
在渐渐淡出
Are fading out right now.
好了 就这样了
Well, that's it.
浪费了3天核对20万张彩票
Three days wasted looking through 200,000 lottery tickets.
那些不是彩票
Those weren't the lottery tickets.
那是个测试
That was a test.
这些才是
These are the lottery tickets.
这是另一个测试么
Is this another test?
是滴
Yes.
这些也不是真的彩票
These aren't the real lottery tickets, either.
这些才是真的
These are the real lottery tickets.
所以为了买20万张彩票
So, in addition to buying 200,000 lottery tickets,
你还打印了40万张假彩票
you had 400,000 fake ones printed up?
我必须要确保
I had to be sure.
天啊 我们赢了
Oh, my God. We won!
什么 让我看
What?Let me see that.
耶 我们赢了
Yes! We won the lottery!
我要给我的JJ找个管家
I'm getting a penis butler.
有什么事 先生
Sir?
好吧 给我的JJ当管家 给它当管家
All right,butle my penis.Butle it!
这太棒了
This is awesome.
现在我们有钱了
Now that we're rich,
我们的好日子要开始了
our lives are going to be so much better.
你确定兑现那张
You sure it was such a good idea
奖金支票是个好注意么
to cash that lottery check?
我觉着把所有的钱摆在家里看上去很2
It seems foolish to have all this money lying around.
哦 那你宁愿把钱放在银行
Oh, you'd rather have it down at the bank
然后犹太人可以觊觎它们么
where the Jewish guys can leer at it?
耶 太棒了
Yeah!All right!
钱啊
Money!(whistling)
Whoo-hoo!Whoo!
讽刺美国都是一些犹太人在操纵金融界
谁啊
(phone rings)Hello?
- 你们把钱挥霍光了么 - 没 爸爸
- Did you blow all your money yet? - No, Daddy.
好吧 你们挥霍光了再打给我
All right.Call me when you blow all your money.
爱你 再见
Love you. Bye.
好了 我们怎么花我们的奖金
All right,so how are we going to spend our winnings?
我要去买很多超市炸鸡
I'm going to get some supermarket fried chicken
然后吃到我恶心
and eat it until I'm nauseous.
我终于可以给我的女孩买她一直想要的小饰品了
I'm going to finally get my gal that doodad she's been wantin'!
我要在买一大张镜子放在地上
I'm going to get a floor mirror to squat over
然后看看到底是什么东西弄出来的噪音(看床下的妖怪么)
and see what's making all that noise.
好了 都给我冷静
Okay, everybody just calm down.
我们不会疯狂的花这些钱的
We're not going to go crazy spending our winnings,
我们不能让它改变了我们
and we're not going to let this money change us.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
这些钱是我们去往幸福生活的车票 就从现在开始
This money is our ticket to the good life, starting now.
我刚买了一大屋子来放金币
I just bought a giant room full of gold coins,
我要跳入其中 就像Scrooge McDuck一样
and I'm going to dive into it like Scrooge McDuck.
史高治 麦克老鸭Scrooge(吝啬鬼) McDuck 唐老鸭的叔叔
恶搞了其动画中在金币里跳水游泳的一段
阿 这不是液体的
Aah! It's not a liquid!
是许多片固体物质
It's a great many pieces of solid matter
组成的就像坚硬地板一样的表面
that form a hard,floor-like surface!
Aah!
Peter 你在这做什么
Peter, what are you doing here?
你不是应该在上班么
Shouldn't you be at work?
我辞职了 Lois
I quit my job, Lois.
- 你什么 - 是啊 我们现在有钱了
- You what? - Yeah,we're rich now.
我不需要工作了
I don't need to be working.
啊 你要是当时在场就好了 Lois
Ah,you should've been there,Lois.
我告诉Angela她该怎么处置那份工作
I told Angela what she could do with that job,
就像我以前一直幻想的那样
just like I always fantasized.
Angela 我只想好好谢谢你
Angela,I just want to thank you
让我度过了这么多
for several extremely pleasurable years
在这里工作的极度愉快的日子
working for this corporation.
呃 发生了一些意外
Uh,certain unexpected developments
让我
have created a situation
不需要在这工作了
where I am no longer in need of employment.
呃 不管怎样
Uh,I would be remiss,however,
如果不表达出我的谢意
if I did not extend my gratitude to you
对于您给我的始终不渝的公正和信任 会显得我没心没肺
for your unwavering fairness and belief in me,
对了 你的桌上有一泡巨屎
and there is a giant poo on your desk.
嘿 Horace 再给大家来一轮
Hey,Horace,another round for everybody.
天哪 Peter 你真是
Gosh, Peter,you're really
对你的钱很大方啊
being generous with your money.
嘿 如果你不能和你的朋友分享
Hey,what's the point of being rich
那成为富人又有什么意义呢 是吧
if you can't share it with your pals, huh?
好 等下 我想到一个
Okay, wait,I-I got one.
你更愿意和谁嘿咻
Who would you rather do?
是Susan Boyle(英国达人的苏珊大妈)
Susan Boyle or a sex doll
还是在一群兄弟会成员中传了一遍的充气娃娃
that's been passed around a fraternity?
呃 他们清理过那娃娃么
Well,have they been cleaning the doll?
得了吧 他们都是贝塔兄弟会会员 全是些野兽
Please, these guys are Betas--they're total animals.
嘿 我想到一个 Peter
Hey,I got one,Peter.
你更愿意做什么
What would you rather do?
原地踩水(一种游泳姿势 这里指坐吃山空)
Tread water where you are right now
还是在18个月里
or increase your net worth fivefold
让你的财富值净增五倍
within the next 18 months?
什么
Huh?
什么 我…你在说什么呀
What?I... what are you talking about?
嗯 我朋友Marty是个化学高手
Well,my friend Marty is a whiz with chemistry,
他说 他研究出一种
and he says he's come up
新的增大JJ的药物
with a new penis enlargement pill,
而且如果我们能给他提供10万刀的启动资金
and if we can bankroll him $100,000 in startup money,
他可以在一年内把它变成3倍
he'll triple our investment in a year.
嗯 呃…上帝 我…我 我不知 呃…
Well,uh...gee,I-I'm...I don't,uh...
Peter 我已经冒昧地
Peter, I've taken the liberty
模拟出了预销售额
of mocking up some sales projections.
哇 太棒了
Wow, that's pretty good.
然后这是我们将得到的利润
And this would be our net profits.
呀
Yikes.
你知道 Peter 呃
You know, Peter, uh,
马上是Bonnie的生日了 而且如果我没
Bonnie's birthday is coming up,and I'll be gol-darned
按承诺她的那样请Stevie Nicks
if I didn't go ahead and promise her that Stevie Nicks
西方摇滚乐坛一位响当当的人物
加州知名乐团Fleetwood Mac的灵魂人物
到我们家然后给她唱3首歌 我就死定了
would come to our house and sing three songs to her.
啊 我还真是个大嘴巴 不是么
(chuckling):Boy,do I got a big mouth,huh?
是啊 如果你准备为老婆开口
Yeah,if you're going to open your mouth with the missus,
然后一直热吻 是吧
stick to kisses, huh?
(笑得真假啊)
真是幽默啊 太搞笑了
What neat humor.What neat humor.
那你怎么说 Peter 你们帮我们么
So what do say,Peter?Can you help us out?
当然了 你们两个笨蛋
Of course I can, you dope.
我们是好兄弟 不是么
We're pals, right?
给
There you go.
嘿 Horace 给我们
Hey,Horace,give us
给我们3杯你最好的波旁威士忌
three shots of your best bourbon.
然后让我喜欢的那个俄罗斯侍者送过来
And have that Russian waiter I like bring it over.
La la la la la la la la la la la
Trololo
恶搞了俄国人Eduard Khil一个网络走红视频Trololo
La la la la la la la la la la la
Ho ho ho ho ho
La la la la la la la la la la la la
La la la la la la la la la la
Ah la la la
La la la la la la
La la la la la
Bop ba da da da da da da da
La la la la la la.
啊 你从那笑容里绝对猜不出
Boy,you wouldn't guess from that smile
他所有的孩子都流产了 是吧
that all his kids were stillborn, huh?
好了 那么 再次感谢你 Peter
All right,well,thanks again, Peter.
我得走了
I got to head out.
我告诉我妈要去医院里看她
I told my mother I'd visit her in the hospital.
嗯 我得去工作了
Yeah, and I got to work.
我今晚要飞Minneapolis
I'm flying a leg to Minneapolis tonight.
明尼阿波利斯 美国明尼苏达州东南部城市
哦
Oh.
好吧 我…我了解了
Yeah, I-I-I understand.
你们…你们有其他事要做
You... you've got other things to do.
我…我刚给你们写了支票
I-I just wrote you guys a couple of checks,
但是 不 你…你们去做自己的事吧
but no, you... you-you-you do your things.
- 什么 - 没什么 我是说 我…就说说
- What? - No, I mean, I-I'm just saying,
我…我觉得朋友应该一起玩 然后一起做点什么
I-I thought friends hang out,do things with each other.
你知道 尤其是当其中一个
You know,especially when one friend
给了其他人一大笔钱时
gives the other friends a whole bunch of money.
哦 呃 我想我可以再待会
Oh.Well,I guess I could stick around.
嗯 我…我想副驾驶应该可以自己飞的
Yeah,and I-I guess the co-pilot can fly the plane.
她是个女的 乘客对这个完全不在意
She's a woman and passengers are usually okay with that.
我有次看到了一个除臭剂广告
I once saw a deodorant commercial
里面有个女飞行员
that had a woman pilot.
这样还差不多
That's more like it.
从现在起 我们要做所有我想做的事
From now on,we're all gonna do whatever I want to do.
因为我是那个有钱的家伙
'Cause I'm the one with the dough.
行 我觉得蛮公平的
Okay, I guess that's fair.
好滴 因为我想做的就是
Good.'Cause what I want to do is
呆在这喝醉看电视
stay here,get drunk and watch TV.
现在我们回到过敏期间的Michael McDonald
We now return to Michael McDonald During Allergy Season.
美创作型歌手 5次获得格莱美奖
Haa...
Haa-haa...
Haa-haa-haa-haa-haa...
Haa...
Haa-chu!
嘿Peter 你让我看完整个第一季
Hey, Peter, you wanted me to watch the entire first season
《真爱如血》然后告诉你哪里有露点
of True Blood and come show you where there was boob?
一部讲吸血鬼的大尺度美剧
是啊 我不想看
That's right, I don't want to see
什么实在的《真爱如血》 只想看里面的波波
any actual True Blood, just boob.
恩 那么 我找到一些
Yeah, well, I found some.
不
No!
Anna Paquin的波不能算真的
Anna Paquin boob does not count as real boob!
演员 《真爱如血》里的女猪脚
那看起来就像一个12岁男孩的
That's like looking at a 12-year-old boy.
天啊 你早该知道的 Joe
Geez. Y-You should know that, Joe!
你绝对应该知道的
You should definitely know that!
抱歉 Peter
Sorry, Peter.
抱歉又不能让我看到值得看的咪咪
Sorry doesn't show me nipples worth seeing!
然后该说你了 Anna 你真是糟透了 你那电视剧也是如此
And as for you,Anna,you're dreadful and so is the program.
又不是我写的
I didn't write it.
嗯 但是你认识他们
Yeah,but you know the people who do.
那个 Alan Ball 你认识他 对吧
That Alan Ball-- you know him, right?
给美剧《六尺之下》《真爱如血》做过编剧
是啊
Yeah.
为什么他写的东西
How come everything he writes
- 都那么沮丧 - 我怎么知道
- is so dreary? - I don't know.
告诉他让他振作起来 事情没那么糟的
Tell him to cheer up!Things ain't so bad!
这集好怪哟
This is a weird episode.
好了 Quagmire 我要你咬第一口
Okay, Quagmire,I want you to take the first bite
这个巧克力软糖冰棒
out of this fudge pop,
因为第一口是最疼的
because that first bite is the one that really hurts.
那好吧
Well, okay.
Ah! Ow!
Ow!
嗯 叫的对 嗷
Yeah, that's right "Ow."
现在你把它吞下去
Now, you swallow that.
你敢吐出来试试
Don't you dare spit that out.
这又有什么区别
What's the difference?
你已经得到你想要的了
You got what you wanted.
我说吞下去
I said swallow it!
现在 把你脸上剩下的涂开
Now,smear what's left of it on your face
然后张嘴看着我
and look at me with your mouth open.
看看你自己 你这下流的妓女
Look at yourself,you filthy whore.
我现在甚至都不想吃它了
I don't even want this now.
好了 大伙们 你们现在要演绎一段同步的二重唱
Okay,guys,now you're gonna do a synchronized duet
来自"Makin' Whoopee" 与此同时我要用BB枪射你们
of "Makin' Whoopee" while I shoot you with this BB gun.
一首爵士蓝调 出自1928年的音乐剧Whoopee!
听起来不是很安全
That doesn't sound safe.
开始
Action!
- 另一位新娘 - 她看起来很欢乐
- Another bride - She looks so gay
- 另一个六月 - 哦 多好的一天
- Another June - Oh, what a day
另一个阳光明媚的蜜月
Another sunny honeymoon
臀部摇起…
Hip hip hoor...
另一个季…
Another seas...
另一个原因
Another reason
可以欢呼
For making whoopee
听着 你不准备射我们的眼睛 是吧 Peter
Look,you aren't gonna shoot us in the eye,are you,Peter?
当然不 Joe
Oh, no, Joe.
我不会去射你们眼睛的
I wouldn't try to shoot you in the eye.
- 许多鞋子 - 我们在扔鞋子
- A lot of shoes - We're throwing shoes
- 许多大米 - 也非常可爱
- A lot of rice - It's all so ni...
Peter 刚才差点射中我的眼睛
Peter,it was really close to my eye!
放松 Joe
Relax, Joe.
我射哪都不会射你眼睛的
I'm nowhere near your eye.
嘿 Joe 睁开眼
Hey, Joe, open your eye.
骗到你了
Gotcha.
搞毛啊Peter 你射中他的眼睛了
What the hell,Peter?!You shot him in the eye!
继续唱 你 把你下巴抬起来
Keep singing,you.And keep your chin up,
这样我能看见你的喉结
so I can see your throat.
不 老子不干了 你就是个混蛋
No,no screw this!You're a jerk!
混蛋 你怎么能这样
Jerk? What kind of a way is that
给你钱的朋友呢
to talk to your friend who gives you money?
去死吧 Peter
Go to hell, Peter!
我们不需要你的钱
We don't need your money!
也不需要你这样的朋友
And we don't need friends like you!
是 我们走了
Yeah! We're out of here!
好吧 随便 我不在乎
Fine, go on. I don't care.
我不需要你们 爷有的是钱
I don't need you, I got money!
你知道么 Peter 你过去是个很好的家伙
You know,Peter,you used to be a great guy.
但自从你赢了彩票
But ever since you won that lottery...
走吧Joe
Come on, Joe!
艹他 啊
fuck this guy!Aah!
我是来着面试《屋顶上的小提琴手》的
I'm here to audition for Fiddler on the Roof.
1905年的音乐剧 这家伙是个犹太人
极其吝啬 显然看上Peter的钱了
进来吧
Come right in.
Peter 上帝啊 你他娘的穿的什么东西啊
Peter,my God,what the hell are you wearing?
这是套纯金打造的晚礼服 Lois
It's a solid gold tuxedo, Lois.
我得和那3个饶舌歌手为这个斗歌
I had to fight three rappers
在废话商店那的
down at the Nonsense Store for this.
听着 Peter 这不是真正的我们
Look,Peter,this is not who we are.
我担心那奖金正在改变我们家
I'm worried the money is changing this family,
而且不是你希望的那种
and not the way you hoped.
呃 我想这样可以让你闭嘴 那么你说对了
Well,I was hoping it would make you shut up,so you're right.
告诉你 我今天早上和Bonnie谈过了
You know,I spoke to Bonnie this morning,
然后她说你2周都没和Joe或者Quagmire说过话了
and she said you haven't talked to Joe or Quagmire in two weeks.
谁在乎啊 我不需要Quagmire
Who cares?I don't need Quagmire.
我当然也不需要Joe
And I certainly don't need Joe.
我有 钞票Joe
I got Money Joe.
这个笑话不错 钞票Joe
That's a good one, Money Joe!
我不喜欢这些钱带我给我们
I don't like what this money is doing to us.
甚至影响到了Brian和Stewie
It's even affecting Brian and Stewie.
我想我要打个盹
I think I'm gonna take a nap.
- 什么 在这 - 是啊 我有个巨型风动玩具
- What,here? - Yeah,I had a giant mobile
放在空中 这样我就可以在任何我想睡的地方睡觉了
put in the sky so I can sleep wherever I want.
真惬意啊
This is nice.
我希望马上看到那熊
I hope that bear comes around soon.
那是我的最爱…噢 看呐 熊
That's sort of my fave--Oh, look, the bear!
而且不光是他们
And it's not just them.
Chris也搞出来一些非常奢侈的爱好
Chris has also been developing some very expensive tastes.
模型胶水 先生
Model glue, sir?
嗯 今天有点什么
Well, what do we have today?
今天我们有一款年份稍近的
Today we have a recent vintage procured just this morning
今早刚刚从Michael's爱好商店买的精品
from Michael's Hobby Shop.
嗯 那很棒
Yes,that's very nice.
把我最好的抹布拿来
Bring me my finest rag.
您最爱的抹布 先生
Your fancy rag, sir.
你今晚没事了
You are relieved for the evening.
你可见不着穷人这么做
You don't see poor people doing this!
Lois 你还不明白么
Lois, don't you understand?
我们过去的老问题全都没有了
We don't got any of our old problems anymore.
我们不用操心付账单
We don't have to worry about paying bills,
不用操心节省开支
we don't have to worry about saving dough.
我们只需让自己快乐
All we got to do is enjoy ourselves.
喜欢么
Interested?
上帝呀
Oh, my God.
Peter 这太美了
Peter,it's beautiful!
这是个血钻么
Is it a blood diamond?
一种开采在战争区域并销往市场的钻石
莱昂纳多迪卡普里奥曾经拍过关于血钻的同名电影
啊 最血腥的那种
Ah, the bloodiest.
找到它的两个孩子被迫杀了对方
The two kids who found it were forced to murder each other.
哦 Peter 我爱死它了
Oh,Peter,I love it.
嘿 你想看看他们杀戮的DVD么
Hey,you want to watch a DVD of the murder while we do it?
我已经看过八遍了
I already watched it eight times,
所以我已经知道该抱怨那一部分不好了
so I know exactly which part I want to blam at.
Chris Meg 由于我是个有钱的爹
Chris, Meg, now that I'm a rich father,
然后你们要打动我 然后我对你们保持冷漠
you will try to impress me,and I will remain distant.
开始
Go.
呃 这么说吧 老爸 我告诉过你
Um,say,Dad,did I tell you
我在游艇比赛里得了第二名么
I got second place in the yacht race?
嗯 听起来像某人的爸爸
Hmm.Sounds like somebody's dad
现在比我更开心
is happier than me right now.
那 呃 这个怎么样 老爸
Well, um, how about this, Dad?
学校报纸报道了一个关于我的故事
The school paper is doing a story about me.
那是因为我安排好了的
That's because I had it arranged.
呃 我正在考虑参军
Uh,I was thinking about joining the Army?
不好
No.
Meg 作为一个女孩 你一生就没什么优点
Meg, as a girl,your life holds no merit.
然后 Chris 尽管试吧 你永远也
And,Chris,try as you may,you will never be
不会和你那死去的哥哥一样棒
as good as your older brother who died.
他善于运动和演讲
He was good at sports and talking.
现在 原谅我现在用放大镜看
Now, pardon me while I look at scrimshaw
我的鲸齿雕刻
through a magnifying glass.
啊 都是些勇敢的人
Ah, brave men all.
新贝德福德的浪子们
Lost sons of New Bedford.
美国马萨诸塞州东南部海港
这真是个极好的鲸齿雕刻
That's good scrimshaw.
(巴林顿公园酒店
多次出现在该剧中 编撰的)
啊 我还从未想过每天都在
Ah, I never thought I'd be having high tea
巴林顿公园喝下午茶
at the Park Barrington every single day.
是的 在一大堆白人中吃饭很棒 不是么
Yes, it's nice to eat in a sea of white faces, isn't it?
服务员 让大厨准备好一篮子你们这最好的鱼子酱
Waiter,have the chef prepare a bucket of your finest caviar,
然后带它坐直升机在这个城市里逛一圈
and then give it a helicopter tour of the city.
很好 先生
Very good, sir.
当然很好啦
Very good indeed.
我希望它和我点的缅因州龙虾一样喜欢那旅行
I hope it enjoys it as much as that Maine lobster I ordered.
那边是罗德岛州政府大楼
And over there is the Rhode Island State House,
作为第二大自承重式的大理石穹顶
the second largest self-supporting marble dome
是全球第四大 在梵蒂冈圣彼得大教堂
美国迷你苏达州议会大厦和印度泰姬陵之后
享誉北美
in North America.
我TM的在干什么
Why the fuck am I doing this?
我可以就说我做过就行了
I could've just said I did it.
先生 关于您的账单…
Sir,about your bill...
哦 别担心 Carstairs
Oh, don't worry, Carstairs,
会给你一笔丰厚的小费的
there's ample gratuity on there for you.
才怪
Nyah.
呃 事实上 先生 您的信用卡被拒了
Well,actually,sir,your card has been declined.
真的么
Oh, really?
那我相信给自己的会计打个简短的电话后
Well,I'm sure a brief call to my accountant
这种突如其来的尴尬就会迎刃而解的
will resolve this to our mutual satisfaction.
你好Schnozzenstein
Hello, Schnozzenstein?
应该是个德语系名字 我猜可能是瑞士银行的
我是Peter Griffin
This is Peter Griffin.
我们的信用貌似出了点问题
There seems to be some issue with our credit.
我告诉过Carstairs说你会把一切摆平的
I told Carstairs you'd set everything straight.
你说我破产了是什么意思
What do you mean I'm broke?!
我打到开曼群岛的钱呢
What about all that money I sent to the Gayman Islands?
英属开曼群岛是国际著名的离岸金融中心 很多企业在此注册避税(类似的还有维尔京群岛) 恰好它的名字也是恶趣味的双关语
他们用它干了什么
They did what with it?!
不 我不想要回来了
No, I don't want it back!
我会想你的Carstairs
I'm gonna miss you,Carstairs.
我也会想您的先生
I shall miss you,too,sir.
由于他没有人可以去照顾
With no one to look after,
Carstairs陷入了深深地忧郁
Carstairs fell into a deep depression
但他永远也不显露出来
from which he never emerged.
他两周后死掉了
He died two weeks later.
有人说是他心碎了
Some say of a broken heart.
什么 先生
What, sir?
但那就是Carstairs
But that was Carstairs.
我不敢相信
I can't believe it.
我们失去了一切
We lost everything.
我现在怎么办
What do we do now?
嗯 看来我们最后的希望只有彩票了
Well, seems like our only hope is the lottery.
我勒个X 我们赢了两次 然后又回到这儿了
Holy shit,we won twice and we're right back here again.
我们有1亿5千万然后在1个月里挥霍光了
We had $150 million,and we blew through it in a month.
是啊 但是好的一面是 如果这一切都没有发生
Yeah,but on the bright side,if this hadn't happened,
我们就不会遇到Kyle了
we never would've met Kyle.
嘿
Hey.
- 你好 - 你好 - 嗨 - 好啊
- Hello. - Hey there.- Hi. - What's up?
而且那甚至都不是Kyle
And that's not even Kyle.
Peter 我们不能这样下去了
Peter, we can't live like this.
那我们该怎么做Lois
Well,what are we supposed to do,Lois?
我们拥有的一切都没了
Everything we had is gone!
我们还有朋友 Peter
We have friends, Peter.
不再有了 我们没了
Not anymore, we don't.
他们都是好人
They're good people.
他们会听的
They'll listen.
然后他们会关心我们出了什么事
And they'll care what happens to us,
就算发生了这一切也会的
even after everything that's happened.
你知道 我还够小 你们可以把我
You know,I'm still young enough you can drop me
扔在消防局门口(指弃婴) 无人问津
at the fire station,no questions asked.
哇 哇 看看这是谁
Well, well.Look who it is.
是谁
Who is it?
是我 Peter
It's me, Peter.
我正站在这
I'm standing right here.
这是颗玻璃眼球 Peter
This is a glass eye, Peter.
他们把你射中的那颗切除了
They had to remove the one you shot.
哦 天啊 那真是糟糕的一天 是吧
Oh, boy, that whole day was a mess, huh?
不管怎么说 你怎么了 看起来很糟啊
What happened to you,anyway?You look terrible.
听着 伙计们 我搞砸了
Look,you guys,I messed up bad.
赢得彩票是我和我家庭
Winning the lottery was the worst thing
发生过最糟糕的事
that ever happened to me and my family.
我以为有钱了就能解决所有问题
I thought being rich would solve all my problems,
但是这只让我忘了什么是对我最重要的
but all it did was make me forget what was important.
就像谁是我真正的朋友
Like who my real friends are.
我不指望你们能原谅我
I don't expect you to forgive me,
但是假如 由于某种原因 你们能原谅我的话 我们可以在
but if,for some reason,you do,you can find me
Meeting和Thayer街街角的硬纸箱里找到我
in a cardboard box on the corner of Meeting and Thayer.
Peter 等等
Peter, wait.
去哪里对我来说太远了
That corner's a bit of a hike for me.
我宁愿去你家见你
I'd rather just come see you at home.
什…你哪来这么些钱的
What-- where'd you get this kind of money?
你给我启动资金的那个JJ增大药
The penis enlargement pill you gave me the startup money for.
现在有了不错的利润
It turned a pretty nice profit.
我想我给你我的那份分红很公平
I guess it's only fair that I give you my percentage
这样你就可以拿回你的房子了
so you can get your house back.
Quagmire 我不知道该说什么了
Quagmire, I don't know what to say.
谢谢你
Thank you.
客气了
You're welcome.
如果这样说哪能让你好受点的话 那么这钱花得很值
And if it makes you feel better,it was money well spent.
尽管问问那边的女服务员Sandra
Just ask Sandra the waitress over there.
我们昨晚过得很不错
We had a great time last night.
真是个坚韧的女孩(这药力得有多强啊)
PETER:Tough girl.
竟然还能来上班
Made it into work.
哇 我得说 回家太棒了
Boy,I got to say,it's good to be home.
是啊 尽管有那些起起落落
Yeah.Despite all the ups and downs,
但事情总会好转的
things turned out for the best.
我是说 真的 我们没有比那更糟的了
I mean, really, we're no worse off than we were before.
而且 我们学到了些东西
Plus, we learned something.
这可是用钱买不来的
And you can't put a price on that.
听着 Lois 我们都知道发生了什么
Look, Lois, we all know what happened.
我们都很消沉
We're all depressed.
好吧 让我们去到不同的房间
All right, let's just go to different rooms
然后空洞的看着窗外 不发一言
and stare blankly out the window,saying nothing.
祝贺今晚的彩票获奖者
Congratulations to tonight's sweepstakes winner,
Daniel San Martin Marrero.
- 形状 - 闭嘴
- Shapes.- Shut up.
中文字幕:wudixny 校对:wudixny zurica 注释:wudixny zurica
后期:wudixny 压制:wudixny  @familyguy贴吧字幕组